<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2023-09-10T03:56:06">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Poet</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Be Committed</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>It is so easy to say<br/>The words we utter everyday.<br/>Making promises here and then,<br/>Never had the will to keep it in.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>The vows we made evertime we're moved,<br/>Unspoken words when the preacher stood.<br/>In the altar, there our tears were born;<br/>Hearts were broken and completely torn.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Emotions are swayed and prayers were made,<br/>Hot as a coal once commitments were laid.<br/>Knees were bent, face flat on the floor.,<br/>Then we start with a fervent spirit on our door.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>As time passes by, we slowly turn away<br/>From that on time altar experience we forgert to obey.<br/>Adversity and discouragements had shaken our coast,<br/>And we fall back from the things, Oh completely lost!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>We then realized how hard it is for us,<br/>To stick to our words, to endure and to last.<br/>So quickly we tell that we can fulfill and stay<br/>And then we excuse ourselves with made-up balconey.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Wake up! It is not yet too late,<br/>Do not wallow in your pride or sulk in hate.<br/>For though we fail over and over again,<br/>There's always a second chance for us to win</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>A commitment is not going to be cakewalk.<br/>It's how you do things; not on how you talk.<br/>Even though it is conceived out of emotions,<br/>Yet it can only be detemined through out actions.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>So make amends to God for the things that are undone.<br/>Reconstruct your vows and fulfill them one by one.<br/>Only then miracles start to happen,<br/>For God blesses those who stayed till the end.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
