<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.0.2" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.0.2" modifiedDate="2023-10-29T06:45:28">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>God's Wonderful People</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="c1a">
      <lines>I love the thrill<br/>that I feel<br/>when I get together<br/>with God's wonderful people,</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1b">
      <lines>Love the thrill<br/>that I feel<br/>when I get together with<br/>God's wonderful people,</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1c">
      <lines>What a sight<br/>just to see<br/>all the happy faces<br/>praising God</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1d">
      <lines>In heavenly places;<br/>What a thrill<br/>that I feel<br/>when I get together with<br/>God's wonderful people.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1a">
      <lines>Oh, what joy his love affords when we meet in one accord,<br/>And we lift our hearts in praise unto the Lord;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1b">
      <lines>There's no place I'd rather be<br/>than with the ones who've been set free,<br/>I'm so glad<br/>I'm in God's great big family</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2a">
      <lines>It can be just anywhere two or three are gathered there,<br/>that the spirit of the Lord will be there, too;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2b">
      <lines>there's no fellowship so sweet, there's no thrill that can compete<br/>with the thrill I feel whenever God's children meet.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3a">
      <lines>On that great reunion day when our Lord says, "come away,"<br/>and the saints from ev'ry land sweep through the gates;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3b">
      <lines>Joining loved ones 'round the throne, at last we'll all be gathered home,<br/>that will be the greatest thrill we've ever known.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1e">
      <lines>I love the thrill that I feel when I get together with God's wonderful people,,<br/>Love the thrill that I feel when I get together with God's wonderful people,</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1f">
      <lines>What a sight just to see all the happy faces<br/>praising God<br/>In heavenly places;<br/>What a thrill that I feel when I get together with<br/>God's wonderful people.<br/>I love the God's wonderful people!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
