<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2023-08-25T02:13:54">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Poet1</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>The Purpose</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Amidst the sapphire sky and heavens of gold,<br/>God stares down the earth from above.<br/>He keeps on loosing for devoted and faithful Christians,<br/>who appreciates His sacrifice and cherishes His loves.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>He does not search for people with pride in their hearts,<br/>or men with strong and mighty looks on their face,<br/>who brags of their riches or their high marks<br/>of their intelligence and the winnings of their race.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>What use is a man with high worldly ranks<br/>and invests his money on foolishness and waste.<br/>He is stiffnecked and stubborn in the eyes of God,<br/>for he fills his flesh with what satisfies his taste.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>God simply looks for simple and ordinary people,<br/>who treasure his existence and with merciful hearts,<br/>who firmly commit themselves to God's ministry,<br/>to obligate, to pledge, todo their parts.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Firmly committed means no turning back.<br/>Not to be ashamed no matter what storms will pass.<br/>That's the kinds of Christians God is looking for.<br/>Ready to sacrifice to make their commitment last.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>These Christians who have compassion for the lost.<br/>In tribulations they fight, in trials they rise,<br/>they will forever raise the mighty banner:<br/>"FIRMLY COMMITTED TO THE CAUSE OF CHRIST"</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
